<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="questions">
        <item>App is crashing or I found a bug. What should I do?</item>
        <item>Where should I submit feature requests and suggestions?</item>
        <item>Why does this app not have features like forums, sending friend requests, commenting and other features?</item>
        <item>Why can\'t I see some people\'s anime/manga list?</item>
        <item>I love the app. What can I do to support the development?</item>
        <item>Why do I have to pay for themes? It\'s ridiculous. I will ignore all other features this app offers and rate this app one star just for this.</item>

    </string-array>
    <string-array name="answers">
        <item>Try clearing app data/cache and reinstalling the app. If the problem persists post it in the discord server or leave an email. We will try to solve the issue.</item>
        <item>You can leave any requests or suggestions on discord server.</item>
        <item>Currently the official Mal Api is limited in features and doesn\'t offer any of the social features, forums etc.
        When the Mal Api adds all of this functionality to their Api we will add them to the app as well.</item>
        <item>You can\'t see someone\'s anime/manga list from profile section if it\'s private even if it\'s yours. This data is not provided by the official MAL Api, The app
        uses another unofficial api called jikan api for fetching user list and it does not support fetching private data.</item>
        <item>You can share the app and leave a review. Or you can also help translate this app to your language. It would help a lot 😃</item>
        <item>If you want to do that please go ahead. It\'s not uncommon for apps to have paid themes and there are many out there which do so.
        If you want free dark theme or other theme options. You can check out other MAL clients like moelist and MalClient on playstore.</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>