<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="questions">
        <item>The app is crashing/ I found a bug.</item>
        <item>I purchased Pro version but I still see ads.</item>
        <item>Where should I submit feature requests and suggestions?</item>
        <item>Why does this app not have features like forums, sending friend requests, commenting and other features?</item>
        <item>Why can\'t I see some people\'s anime/manga list?</item>
        <item>I love the app. What can I do to support the development?</item>
        <item>Why do I have to pay for themes? I will rate this app one star just for this.</item>
        <item>How to contact the developer? / How to get help?</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="answers">
        <item>Try clearing the app data, cache and reinstalling the app. Maybe even try restarting your device afterwards. If the problem persists, post it in our Discord server or send an email. Some (hopefully ☜(ﾟヮﾟ☜) ) kind individuals will try their best to help you out. 😃</item>
        <item>Try clearing the app data and cache, If that doesn\'t work reinstall the app.</item>
        <item>You can leave any requests or suggestions on our Discord server.</item>
        <item>Currently the official MAL API (the interface required for exchanging data with the website) is limited in features and doesn\'t offer any of the social features. If/ When MAL adds those to their API, we will add them to the app as well.</item>
        <item>You can\'t see someone\'s anime/ manga list from profile section if it\'s private, even if it\'s your own. This data is not provided by the APIs used.</item>
        <item>You can share the app and leave a review. You can also help translate this app into your native language if it\’s not yet translated. That would help a lot! 😃</item>
        <item>There have been a few people complaining about the app\’s payment and advertising model. It\'s not uncommon for apps to have paid themes and there are many out there which do so. It also helps keep the development alive and supports the developer. If you want free dark theme or other theming options, you can check out other MAL clients by other cool devs like MoeList (by axiel7) and MALClient (by Drutol).</item>
        <item>Have a look in the About App section for email (feedback) and Discord server details</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>